myblueprint.ca 2017-03-02

# Privacy Policy | myBlueprint

Internet Explorer 6 users: [upgrade your browser](http://www.microsoft.com/windows/internet-explorer/default.aspx) for a significantly improved experience. 

### Privacy Policy

**Our Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information when you use our service.** When you log into www.myBlueprint.ca using your school Activation Key or when you select your school from the Board Landing Page and create a “My Profile” (Profile), you have access to a resource that allows you to create goals and plans of action, save high school plans, track your progress towards graduation, save post-secondary opportunities and occupations of interest and other education planning related features. At this time, we collect the personal information such as: your name, email address, gender and grade. We may also ask you about your preferences for using our site, including whether or not you wish to receive newsletters and other information by email. To personalize your Profile and to enable potential features, we may in the future ask you for your date of birth, place of birth, student number and information about your hobbies and interests. We will also know, based on your Activation Key, your school and the city and province in which you go to school, and we may combine that information with information we have from your Profile.

We collect this information for a number of purposes: to send you occasional newsletters, to customize the content that you see, to provide you with information on a variety of relevant subjects including scholarships, jobs and health information, to conduct surveys and to offer promotions in which contestants may win prizes.

**We will not use your personal information for any other purpose without your consent (unless we are required to do so by law).**

### Cookies

We collect non-personal information and data automatically through the standard operation of our Internet servers and through the use of “cookies”. Cookies are small text files containing a unique identification number that identifies your browser – but not you – to our servers each time you visit our website. Cookies are not pervasive or invasive programs that enter a user’s system and damage files. They simply tell us which pages of our website are visited and by how many visitors. Cookies cannot, by themselves, disclose the individual identity of any user, and we never combine information gathered by a cookie with personally identifiable information like your name, telephone number or email address, without your consent.

### Use of Information by Others

**We do not sell your personal information.** We do not share it with others unless we have your permission to do so and, in some cases, if it has been approved by your School Board.

We may permit others to offer subscription and/or registration-based services through our website. Doublethink Inc. is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties, and you should check the Privacy Policy of such party before providing any personal information. We may transfer your personal information if Doublethink Inc. is acquired by or merged with another company; in that case, we will notify you prior to your personal information being transferred.

### External Links

This website contains links or references to other websites to which this Privacy Policy does not apply. These sites are not owned or controlled by us and we are not responsible for the collection, use and disclosure of personal information or the privacy practices of other parties or other websites to which our site may refer visitors or provide links. When submitting personal information on other websites, we encourage you to read the Privacy Policy of those sites.

### Confidentiality and Security

We use physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information. However, no security measures are perfect and we cannot be held liable if security is breached by an End User or any other person. Please keep your login credentials (email and password) safe and private.

We limit access to your personal information to employees who reasonably need to come in contact with that information for the purposes set out above.

### Updating Your Account Information

If you want to update your personal information, use the “Account Details” section in your Profile and make changes online at any time.

### Opt-Out Option

You can stop using our website at any time. You may cancel your account by clicking the “Delete Account” button the Account Details section in your Profile. Upon your request, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to functionally delete your personal information from our database. However, it may be impossible to delete a user’s entry without some residual information because of backups and records of deletions.

### Your Consent

We will not collect or use your personal information without your consent (unless we are required to do so by law). By agreeing to the provisions of the End User License Agreement, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you are consenting to the collection and use of your personal information as set out in this Privacy Policy. You may withdraw your consent to our collection and use of your personal information at any time, subject to contractual and legal restrictions and reasonable notice. However, please note that if you withdraw your consent to certain uses of your personal information, we may no longer be able to provide products or services to you.

### Minors

When a person under age 12 attempts to create a profile on www.myBlueprint.ca, a parent or legal guardian must contact us to provide consent to the collection and use of the user’s personal information. We will not contact individuals under age 12 for marketing purposes without the permission of a parent or legal guardian.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, or if you would like to review your personal information, you can contact us at: [info@myBlueprint.ca](mailto:info@myBlueprint.ca)

3376A Yonge Street  
Toronto, Ontario  
M4N 2M8  
Canada  
416-901-5555

Any dispute arising between you and Doublethink Inc. with respect to privacy is subject to the terms and conditions of use and this Privacy Policy, including limitations on damages, arbitration and application of the laws of the Province of Ontario. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the policy changes on our website. Site visitors are advised to periodically check this website for such changes.
